{"instructions": ["This section is an extended version of the previous task, which is clicking on <strong>left to right</strong> or <strong>right to left</strong> to indicate the moving direction of the sound beep. <p></p>In cases where you can not tell, just give your best guess.", "When you are ready, click <strong>Continue</strong> to hear the first sound beep."], "feedback": true, "holdfeedback": false, "feedbackdur": 600, "serveraudio": false, "estimatedduration": 4, "randomize": false, "isi": 600, "volume": [{"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "To begin, please use the same volume as in the previous task.<p> Click <strong>Continue</strong> to proceed.</p>", "choices": ["Continue"]}, {"plugin": "html-button-response", "prompt": "Is the right headphone in your right ear, and the left headphone in your left ear? It is very important!", "choices": ["Yes, let's continue."]}], "trials": [{"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/32us_2_Uch3Tmk4PV0fqjhk.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "32us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/4us_2_AXX66NzUmNu0ONfb.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "4us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/32us_1_pa8bo4C1iEwmr0Rd.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "32us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/64us_2_LLfghxlzXEgcW2jL.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "64us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/64us_1_P2KPmaihn3Ub0D6e.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "64us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/4us_2_CXzwuZvjrOJ72dQL.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "4us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/4us_1_ORHMlEr8ORRqyBy4.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "4us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/32us_2_CamK0ybphnZzZquA.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "32us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/2us_1_4Aee04zZd6bXOtxP.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "2us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/128us_2_69wrf7KGXWFicQ6u.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/2us_1_RqafJfbp9je33MBf.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "2us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/2us_1_mehNvvfaFTnpXTkU.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "2us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/32us_1_EDvVKUfCt2Muh6bD.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "32us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/8us_1_187fjtMlPyxeltnQ.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "8us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/16us_2_39tDPA5YmYRuOXsU.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "16us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/128us_1_eNUii0hhR2gAFs9H.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/2us_1_jyc5UBQTlovRWMQL.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "2us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/128us_1_NiunMxZL18Yfka2W.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/4us_1_IUHzTfeDvr1p01lO.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "4us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/2us_1_pUEB9c1zmC4PPh9c.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "2us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/32us_1_PV0xOxFuPUf3bvlz.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "32us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/16us_1_lXaaXZvXOKXR3UCH.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "16us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/32us_2_qHM5fpNwm7d1FFIU.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "32us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/16us_2_72p2rkE2huhRgwKl.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "16us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/32us_2_oe2oqCmCPX9KHx1B.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "32us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/64us_2_mj9ImLyRMaMnry4V.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "64us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/8us_1_7Va346MPZMSn0sCP.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "8us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/16us_2_drYWXvNIO8PuZePN.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "16us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/8us_2_YF34EuUQXOmDmZMR.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "8us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/8us_2_OomBjpA3tUyuyu2H.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "8us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/4us_2_4T9KjYOrcW9nweva.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "4us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/2us_1_LcdizgBbzSJLRIKf.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "2us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/8us_2_j8O3uPdafDxIxo9w.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "8us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/128us_2_nK8fYNhfk9yWXDUR.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/64us_1_ezkIP89qvHN5fjbL.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "64us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/4us_2_J5I71QDLnsjeggYq.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "4us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/8us_2_Tn1IEUh0qQtYTOS4.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "8us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/128us_2_QTa0EKVuRU2XMNlg.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/128us_1_tClhankY8aEfhVwX.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/64us_2_NLDbVR8cZkyAteD5.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "64us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/128us_2_VtZIR7Onbg3TcisN.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/64us_1_2I9BPq4QO62ap9dx.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "64us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/16us_2_4qzY4OF40jW3Cm9M.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "16us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/16us_2_um8UHQw8C4dxK6RL.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "16us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/8us_2_QGLudR5sWW4is5rN.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "8us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/16us_1_7j2Co4IaheUKXIv5.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "16us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/4us_1_h1767rcXW0AxqcQV.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "4us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/32us_2_l77rz6vgGWxUtGNq.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "32us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/4us_1_XDxIgBQXV61rzg0C.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "4us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/8us_2_STS8mXjCAiFThFzS.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "8us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/128us_2_2OSdWKFAQOlhxelE.wav", "cond": 1, "annot": {"ITD": "128us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/16us_1_uqWN8tdt2Ch998cy.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "16us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/2us_2_Lfl7yHByGjXTjJe4.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "2us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/2us_1_McaJygC5UAE6tWil.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "2us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 2, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/64us_2_H8rEApGtgVVGjMQQ.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "64us"}}, {"plugin": "hari-audio-button-response", "prompt": "In which <strong>direction</strong> did the sound travel?", "choices": ["left to right", "right to left"], "answer": 1, "stimulus": "https://speech-in-noise-test.s3.us-east-2.amazonaws.com/audios/ITD/main/64us_1_qUcV0wOkZuzuLZD6.wav", "cond": 2, "annot": {"ITD": "64us"}}]}